(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Promise 2 You
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Slicing through the asphalt with my tires
暗闇走り抜ける
I drive through the darkness
チープなスリルに身を任せても
Even if I surrender myself to cheap thrills
明日に怯えていたよ
I was frightened of tomorrow
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone else's sake
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何も怖くはない
There is nothing to fear
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは
Alone,
解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Holding the unsolvable puzzle of love
Get wild and tough
この街で
In this city,
やさしさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to rely on kindness
Get chance and luck
君だけが
Only you
守れるものがどこかにあるさ
Can find something somewhere to protect
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも
Even alone,
傷ついた夢を取り戻すよ
I will take back my wounded dream
ありきたりな僕の日々を
Destroy my mundane days,
壊してくれ
please.
異常なほどの刺激を
I was waiting for an extraordinary
待ち望んでいたんだな
stimulation, wasn't I?
ちょっとしたそんな冒険心は
That little sense of adventure
改札に吸い込まれて
was sucked into the ticket gate.
吐き出された辿り着いた
Spat out, I arrived in
雨降るこの街
this rainy city.
何も感じないまま
Feeling nothing as I go on,
死んでいくのはごめんだ
I refuse to just die like this.
終わりのその先を目指して
Aiming for what lies beyond the end...
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Run out, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは確かなまま
We remain certain,
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, Steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, Steppin' out tonight,
追いかけてんだ
chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
また首を突っ込んで
Sticking my neck out again,
見事に散らかしてんだ
I've made a splendid mess of things.
曖昧で退屈な
Saying goodbye to these vague
気持ちとさらばさ
and boring feelings.
関係ないって顔したって
Even if you act like it doesn't concern you,
どこかで繋がっていて
we are connected somewhere.
何度だって引き戻すと
Trying to pull me back again and again,
手招くこの街
this city beckons.
ビリビリ痺れるような
Like an electric shock,
今を生きていたいんだ
I want to live in this moment.
極限のギリギリで行こうぜ
Let's go to the extreme edge!
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Run out, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは確かなまま
We remain certain,
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, Steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, Steppin' out tonight,
追いかけてんだ
chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
Inside, outside, just wanna feel good everyday
Inside, outside, I just wanna feel good everyday
Inside, outside, I just wanna feel alive
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight
Run out, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは確かなまま
We remain certain,
輝く Steppin' out tonight
Shining, Steppin' out tonight.
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Tomorrow is waiting for us.
抗え Steppin' out tonight
Resist, Steppin' out tonight!
僕らは風の中
We are in the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight
Even so, Steppin' out tonight,
追いかけてんだ
chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
Don't take your love away, you ain't heard nothing yet
Don't take your love away
Wake up, wake up, bang!
まだ滲み出した表示は
The display that has just started to bleed,
あなた今忙しいの？
are you busy right now?
既読の毒とLove Co-m-o-i-b-i
Read receipt poison and Love, Come on baby.
世話しない 邪魔をしないで頂戴
Don't bother me with your meddling.
大切にめくれた カワイイ
Preciously peeled back, cute
逃げ場がない魂
There is no escape for my soul.
甘い言葉かけるよりも
Rather than whispering sweet words,
ずっと愛しい
You are far more beloved.
息も詰まるほど
Enough to suffocate me,
求めて離さないで
Desire me and never let me go.
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough,
いっそ殺して
So just kill me instead.
Fatal Action
あなたを手に掛けて
Take you into my hands,
Infatuation
呼吸さえ仕留めて
Steal even your breath.
Dedication
このまま Addiction
Just like this, Addiction,
して まだ たった一口でしまい
And it's not over with just one bite.
Fatal Action
あなた口をつけて
Put your lips on it,
Infatuation
そのまま飲み込んで
Swallow it down just like that.
Dedication
すぐ様 Addiction
Instant Addiction,
して ほら たった一口
Come on, just one bite.
死ぬほど愛したいだけ
I just want to love you to death.
Don't take your love away
You wake up nothing yeah
Wake up makeup bang bang
Uh, 吐き出そう 愛情過多でいい
Uh, let it out, excessive love is fine.
あなたには私しかいない
You have no one but me.
Uh, take it off 愛情が足りない
Uh, take it off, love is lacking.
私にはあなたしかいないんだ
I have no one but you.
飲んで満たした
I drank and filled myself.
この手掴んだ
I grabbed this hand.
まだ未練があるのね
You still have regrets, don't you?
あんたが
You are...
Wagamama
Selfish.
愛と名付けて
Named it love,
私ハイする
And I get high.
あなたに溺れてく
Drowning in you,
息苦しいくらいに
To the point of suffocation,
浸水させて
Let me submerge.
いっそ壊して
So just break me instead.
Fatal Action
私を手に掛けて
Take me into your hands,
Infatuation
キスで口塞いで
Seal my mouth with a kiss.
Dedication
まだまだ Addiction
More and more Addiction,
して まだ たった一口
And still, just one bite.
非合理的愛
Irrational love.
覗く眼差し込めて
With a staring gaze,
躊躇いなど捨てて
Throw away hesitation.
Dedication
すぐ様 Addiction
Instant Addiction,
して ほら たった一口
Come on, just one bite.
これで終わらせないで
Don't let it end with this.
Our love continued further evolve more
My love is besotted with you
Your love continued further evolve more
More but more yes I'm a little confused
これはあんたの所為や
This is your fault.
どうあがいても私は
No matter what I do,
二人はただ愛されたかっただけだったのすれ違い
We just wanted to be loved, a misunderstanding.
いらないそういう言葉は期待するだけ無駄
I don't need those words, expecting them is useless,
だとしてしまった愛の形が
Assuming that, the shape of love
分からないよね
is something you don't understand, right?
たまらなくなるほど
Becoming unbearable,
求めて離さないで
Desire me and never let me go.
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough,
いっそ殺して
So just kill me instead!
Fatal Action
あなたを手に掛けて
Take you into my hands,
Infatuation
呼吸さえ仕留めて
Steal even your breath.
Dedication
このまま Addiction
Just like this, Addiction,
して まだ たった一口でしまい
And it's not over with just one bite.
Fatal Action
ただ口をつけて
Just put your lips on it,
Infatuation
そのまま飲み込んで
Swallow it down just like that.
Dedication
すぐ様 Addiction
Instant Addiction,
さよなら真っ赤な吐き出しで息が止まるのよな
Goodbye, spitting out crimson, like my breath is stopping.
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights
It's time
As our power grows
Tryin' to stop the show
Might as well go try
Stop time
So you know that we're out there
Swatting lies in the making
Life Will Change
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
Ain't it a shame
I'm not a figment of your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as, I'm just as dangerous
As you so know you'll find
A taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fire inside your head
Your heart
And as your crippled brain
Tries to fight in vain
Your empire will fall
Apart
And you'll know we were out there
Swatting lies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
X-encounter
Lyrics: 黒崎真音 Music: 高瀬一矢
Lyrics: Kurosaki Maon Music: Takase Kazuya
飛べないここからじゃ
I can't fly from here
横顔を眺めてるだけじゃ
Just gazing at your profile
無力さを嘆いても
Even if I lament my powerlessness
この背を誰も押さない
No one will push me forward
Going out
飛び方を忘れていた
I had forgotten how to fly
鳥達の嘆きのvoice
The lamenting voices of the birds
凍てつく無機質な
In this freezing, inorganic
世界に何を望むの
world, what do you wish for?
そうだけどね
Yeah, but you know
確実な希望がもう
A certain hope is already
僕の中に
inside me
Going out
何ができるかなんて
What I can do...
もうやってみなきゃわからない
...I won't know until I try
走り出した始まりへ
Started running towards the beginning
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
Surely it was decided before I was born
羽を揺らし強く地を蹴って
Shaking my wings, kicking the ground strongly
君の元へ羽ばたく RAVEN
Flapping towards you, RAVEN
Fly keep holding on
螺旋のループの中で会う
Meeting inside the spiral loop
この場所で
In this place
もう止められない
Can't be stopped anymore
カルマの真下で
Right under the karma
僕にできることが
What I can do
どんなにわずかでも
No matter how slight it is
その体に背負うもの
The things you carry on that body
その痛み分かち合える日まで
Until the day I can share that pain
君の傍にいる
I will be by your side
絶つ今
Cutting off this moment,
恐れを払って
brushing away the fear.
無常に降り掛かる
Searching for my place,
自分の居場所探して
amidst the heartlessness raining down.
後悔になぞらえた
Likening it to regret,
モノローグ　蝕む夜に見た
I saw it in a night eaten away by monologues.
不器用に風に揺れて
Clumsily swaying in the wind,
僕はまだ弱いまま
I remain weak.
迷って壊れては
Getting lost, breaking apart,
そうやって続く世界へ
that is how the world continues.
たった一つ見つけたら
If I find just one thing,
瞬く星を描き進め
I'll draw a twinkling star and move forward.
闇から覗いた光
Reaching out a hand to the light
手を伸ばして　さあ行こう
peeking from the darkness, let's go.
走り出したこの想い
These feelings that have started running,
ほら　心の星が導いて
look, the star in my heart guides me.
染み付いてる癒えない傷を
The stained, unhealing wounds,
この翼で運び出す RAVEN
I'll carry them out on these wings, RAVEN.
Fly keep holding on
空虚に形のない
Kicking away the empty,
波も蹴散らして
shapeless waves.
凛とした目に宿る灯火を
The light dwelling in those dignified eyes,
曇らせはしない　君はそのままいて
I won't let it cloud over, stay as you are.
向かい風に逆らい
Opposing the headwinds,
小さな羽根広げ目指そう
let's spread our small wings and aim high.
僕ら果てる日まで　共に駆けてゆく RAVEN
We will run together until the day we end, RAVEN.
誰のせいでもない涙
Tears that are no one's fault,
誇りにして　さあ行こう
let's turn them into pride and go.
走り出そう始まりへ
Let's start running toward the beginning,
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
it was surely decided before we were born.
羽根を揺らし強く地を蹴って
Shaking our wings, kicking the earth strongly,
君のもとへ羽ばたく RAVEN
flapping my wings towards you, RAVEN.
Fly keep holding on
何千の後悔の
The heartbeat breathing
あとに息吹く鼓動
after thousands of regrets.
この一瞬が永遠へ変わる
This moment turns into eternity.
手を繋ぎだして　世界を見に行こう
Joining hands, let's go see the world.
皮肉にも僕たちは
Ironically, we will know,
長い夜潜り抜けて知るんだろう
after passing through the long night.
強さの意味を信じ連れた
Bringing the meaning of strength along,
駆けてゆこう
let's run.
遠回り　それは幸福
Taking the long way around is happiness.
どの景色にも愛を持てた時に
When we can hold love for every scenery,
世界はまた生まれ変わる
the world will be reborn again.
Wooo! Hahaha!
Yeah! *Applause*
Thank you so much for watching the anniversary...
Having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments using the hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
Hashtag... Promise2U!
Wait, this way!
This way!
Wrong way, wrong way!
This way? This way!
This way, this way!
Okay. Hashtag Promise2U!
All right.
We're currently at the Promise Hideout!
Whoa!
Look over there!
What the- oh my god that is huge!
Oh my god!
Wow!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
Don't fall! Don't fall!
I'm way too excited!
Don't die! Don't die!
No! It's so big!
Hello everyone!
Is there a helicopter flying out there taking videos of us?
Wow!
Now we have it!
Now we do!
And now that we also have such a fancy stage on the rooftop as well and everything, let's turn things up...
...with some fun variety games!
Variety games!
Yes, it's the variety part!
I bet you guys are probably feeling a bit tired after that intense first half of this live, right?
I'm good!
I'm there! I'm alive! I'm standing!
No, we're good.
We're very...
Ah, you guys seem a little tired.
Yeah.
To help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness, I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys!
Oh!
Mhm. Yes, it's called...
Pleasure or Pain?
Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle!
Woo!
Wait, what does that mean?
Did you say feet?
Each of us will sing the choruses from two songs that we're confident in.
Yeah?
Yes. We'll use the karaoke machine scoring system...
...and the person with the highest combined score will win!
There's also a twist!
I knew it!
Yes. We will be singing while receiving foot massages!
What?!
Yes!
Wait, what?
And how that will affect our performance or score, well...
...we'll see and find out together! Right here!
Oh...
Oh, yay.
Fun!
Yes!
And there will be a punishment for the losers as well, of course.
Oh.
Yes.
Two losers? One winner?
I'm pretty sure that's how it is, yeah.
Okay.
And as for the punishment, the losers...
...will have to drink this super sour Geki-suppa drink!
Geki-suppa juice.
A what?
Geki-suppa juice!
Whoa!
Now let me show you the key item that can make or break this battle!
Here's what we'll use for the first round!
Huh?
Jajan!
It's a foot reflexology mat!
I've never stepped on one of these before.
I have.
It's not pleasant.
It's not fun.
Wait, so you want us to sing while we're on this?
You're gonna sound amazing!
We're all gonna sound amazing singing on this, yes.
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Senpai!
Eh?!
Senpai.
I feel like, you know, you look so beautiful today...
Yeah, that's got nothing to do...
...that came out of nowhere!
What?
You look so amazing.
Oh my god.
Don't you, you know...
I feel like as a senpai you should show us how it's done, right?
Fine, I'll go first. Okay?
Yay!
I'll show you how it's done!
Yeah!
Go!
Alright, so IRyS, which song are you going to sing?
I am going to sing... Zankyou Sanka!
Zankyou Sanka!
Yes.
If you're ready, jump on that mat!
Yes!
Let's- I get on the mat? I get on the mat?
Get on the mat, get on the mat.
Get on the mat.
Ah! Come on, come on.
Don't be dramatic!
Oh! Ah! She's fine!
She's fine!
Ah! I'm on this stuff- ow!
Music start!
That sounds so bad!
You got this!
Yes, you do!
痛てっ！
Ouch!
始まりよ！
It's starting!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
痛てっ！うわっ！
Ouch! Whoa!
あぁー！Oh my god! あぁっ！
Aah! Oh my god! Aah!
Keep walking!
痛った！痛ったー！痛った！
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
痛てっ！やべっ！痛てっ！
Ouch! Oh no! Ouch!
Oh, this part...
あ、痛てっ！
Ah, ouch!
痛てっ！
Ouch!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
An illusionary flower blooming on someone's sleeve,
ただそこに藍を落とした
Only dropped indigo dye there.
派手に色を溶かす夜に
In the night that flashily dissolves colors,
銀朱の月を添えて
Accompanying the vermilion moon.
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind like rolling,
あ、痛てっ！
Ah, ouch!
躓くごとに強くなった
I became stronger every time I stumbled.
光も痛みも怒りも全部
Light, pain, anger, everything!
抱きしめて
Embrace it!
痛ーい！
It huuuurts!
選ばれなければ選べばいい
If you're not chosen, just choose!
声よ轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Voice, roar to the other side of the night!
涙で滲んでた
It was blurred with tears,
あんなに遠くの景色まで
Even to that distant scenery,
響き渡れ
Echo far and wide!
あぁっ！痛った！
Aah! It hurts!
何を奏でて？誰に届けたくて？
What are you playing? Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to remain uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the emotions,
どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how long the conflict,
歌と散れ
Scatter with the song,
残響！
Reverberation!
痛ーい！
It huuuurts!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Good! Right! Good!
Oh, there you go!
How's your blood flow? Do you feel refreshed?
You look great!
Shall we see the score?
This is what she got! Dun-dun!
I've never gotten a score that low before!
70.161. That's so good!
That's good! What are you talking about?
You know 70... That's a B minus.
B minus? That's pretty good!
Isn't it a B minus? That's a C minus.
No, it's a B minus.
Alrighty then. Who wants to go next?
Senpai! Senpai!
We're from the same Gen!
She's Senpai by two hours.
Was it two hours?
I've never heard that from you before.
I'll go! You go!
You're gonna have so much fun!
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you gonna sing for us?
I'm going to be singing Mousou Zei!
Oh! Sakebimashou Mousou Zei!
Oh! Let's shout, Mousou Zei!
I only know old songs. Yay!
That's great! I know that song!
Please start the music! Music Start!
You're gonna be fine!
あの子もいいな　あの子もいいな
That girl is nice, that girl is nice too.
頭の中で　イイコトしてる
Doing 'good things' inside their head.
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？ ah!
Don't you want to make it come true? Ah!
You're on a good spot right now.
あの子でいいや　あの子でいいや
That girl will do, that girl will do.
妥協 大好き　飲む針千本
Love to compromise, swallow a thousand needles.
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
あなたはそれで満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう妄想税
Let's pay the Delusion Tax.
皆様の暮らしを豊かにするために
To enrich everyone's lives.
She's doing it!
叶えたい　たい　たいを現実に
Turn 'want to make it come true' into reality.
今、未来　らい　らいを買い戻せ
Buy back the future now.
アレしたい　したい病も
Even the 'want to do that' disease...
欲しがりも
...and the greed.
さあ、痛い　だいたい　のその向こうへ
Now, let's go beyond the pain.
そう、汚い妄想は
Yes, those dirty delusions...
汚いお金で解決させましょう
...let's resolve them with dirty money.
Yeah! Yeah! Ah!
You did amazing!
I feel like that brought out like a roughness.
How could I actually sing on that?
Oh wow, blood circulation.
That's a lot of blood circulation. Wow.
Alright, the score is in. Let's see what Kronii got.
73.864!
It's still the first half, I can still make it!
Mada zenhan!
It's still the first half!
Oh god, my turn!
I'm excited. I've been wanting to sing this song for so long.
Okay, what song is it?
Fairy Tail! Yakusoku no Hi!
Fairy Tail! The Day of Promise!
Finally! I finally found an instrumental track.
Your childhood, I'm assuming?
Not really. Okay.
Please hop onto the foot reflexology mat.
You ready? Yeah.
Okay, now please start singing. Music Start!
Fairy Tail!
この手で　掴んだ
The light I grasped with this hand...
光は
...is...
Ah! Ah! You're walking! You're walking!
You're great! Yeah, let's go!
夢に描いた理想郷
The utopia I painted in my dreams.
夢のまま終わらせない
I won't let it end as just a dream.
いつか会える　未来の僕に伝えたい
I want to tell the future me that I'll meet someday.
時に未来は残酷で
Sometimes the future is cruel.
鏡のように割れるけど
And breaks like a mirror.
欠片を失くさないよう
So I don't lose the pieces...
見つけ出せばいい
...I just have to find them.
凍える闇が
Even if the freezing darkness...
僕たちの行く手塞いでも
...blocks our path.
きっと忘れない希望
The hope I'll surely never forget.
この手で　掴んだ光は
The light I grasped with this hand...
絆の力　溢れているから
...is overflowing with the power of our bonds.
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know the sad tears.
だから譲れない 揺るがない
That's why we won't yield, we won't waver.
夢見たあの日に
Until that day we dreamed of,
そう辿り着くまで
until we finally reach it.
Yo, you guys can sing on this thing!
It brings out something...
...from deep within.
Okay then...
Since you have something deep within,
it's time to see what score that brought you.
はい！
Yes!
Whoa!
Currently in first place is Hakos Baelz,
with a 81.434 points...
and any comments heading into the second half now?
I'm excited!
I'll continue to do my best...
so that I don't have to do the juice!
頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best!
Alrighty then.
Let me introduce the next key item...
or should I say person for the second half.
In this foot massage battle, yeah?
では、お入りください。どうぞ！
Well then, please come in. Go ahead!
こんにちは。
Hello.
Okay, let me introduce you guys to Takita-san...
who will be giving us foot massages.
A foot massage pro.
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to meet you.
怖いね...
It's scary...
痛いですか？
Does it hurt?
痛いです。
It hurts.
痛いです！？
It hurts!?
Okay, so since it's going to hurt, who wants to kick things off?
Since I went last last time, I'll go first this time.
What are you going to sing?
That is right, that is true.
I'm going to be singing...
馬鹿みたい！
Baka Mitai!
行きます！
Here I go!
Okay then, please get ready.
滝田さんもよろしくお願いします。
Takita-san, we're counting on you too.
優しくしてください。
Please be gentle.
大丈夫。
It's okay.
健康にいいんだから, it's good for your health.
Because it's good for your health, it's good for your health.
Let's go!
はい。
Okay.
Okay then, please start the music! Start!
Inner peace...
Inner peace.
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I've been a fool, such a child.
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt.
You're doing great!
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you're bad at lying,
笑えない笑顔みせた
you showed me a smile that couldn't laugh.
I love youも ろくに言わない
You never even said 'I love you' properly.
口下手でほんまに不器用
Not good with words, truly clumsy.
なのになのにどうして
And yet, and yet, why is it...
サヨナラは言えたの
...that you could say 'goodbye'?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no use, it's no good, it's hopeless.
あんたが好きで好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the alcohol is,
先生！
Teacher!
歪まない思い出が
the unwarped memories...
馬鹿みたい
...make me look like a fool.
痛い！
It hurts!
先生！先生！ありがとうございます！
Teacher! Teacher! Thank you very much!
That's scary. Oh my god.
Alrighty, how was that?
How was the song while getting a foot massage?
I can't feel my big toe.
Now the score is in.
Let's see what you got.
ジャジャン！
Ta-da!
You got a 68.057!
Yay!
That's over 50...
so close to a good number, yeah.
痛い... ありがとうございます。
It hurts... Thank you.
健康になった。
You became healthy.
You became a bit healthy.
You became a lot healthy, yeah.
Is it really that bad? Oh my god.
大袈裟じゃない...
I'm not exaggerating...
やってよ！
You do it then!
I wanna... I wanna try.
Okay! Go!
Before you sit down...
...what song?
Ah, oh yeah.
All righty, please get ready. Takuta-sama, mata yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
All righty, please get ready. Takuta-sama, please take care of me again.
お願いします！
Please take care of us!
ガチ痛い、ガチ痛い。
It really hurts. It really hurts.
I'm... I'm literally...
You're done, you don't have to worry.
Yay! Okay then!
Let's go!
Music Starto!
Music Start!
正しさとは 愚かさとは
What is righteousness? What is stupidity?
それが何か見せつけてやる
I'll show you what that means.
Oh, she's fine!
Oh wow!
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
I've been an honor student since I was small.
気づいたら大人になっていた
Before I knew it, I had become an adult.
ナイフの様な思考回路
With a thought process like a knife,
持ち合わせる訳もなく
I don't have any of that,
でも遊び足りない
but I haven't played enough.
何か足りない
Something is missing.
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
I'm in a bind, this is someone's fault.
あてもなくただ混乱するエイデイ
Aimlessly, just confused every day.
それもそっか
That's true too,
最新の流行は当然の把握
keeping up with the latest trends is a given.
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking economic trends on the commute.
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joined the company with a pure heart to work,
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
it's a natural rule for a working adult.
はぁ？
Hah?
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
あなたが思うより健康です
I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸な
Everything is mediocre,
あなたじゃ分からないかもね
you might not understand.
嗚呼よく似合う
Ah, it suits you well,
その可もなく不可もないメロディー
that neither good nor bad melody.
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
頭の出来が違うので
Since our intelligence is different,
問題はナシ
there's no problem.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
You didn't seem like you were in a massage.
マッサージされてる？
Was I getting a massage?
I feel so good! Yay!
えっ、マジ？
Eh, seriously?
All righty then, the scores are in again.
Let's see what you got. Result onegaishimasu.
Let's see what you got. Result please.
Ja-jan!
Ta-da!
Yay!
She got a 77.994!
That's so good!
All right, well, who's left?
We only have one person left!
IRyS-ke!
It's IRyS!
行きなさい、早く。
Go on, quickly.
What song are you singing?
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko because the world is just that cruel.
世界は残酷です。
The world is cruel.
先生、もう本当に思いっきりやってください。
Sensei, please really go all out.
優しくしてください。
Please be gentle.
強く！
Strong!
強くて！
Stronger!
All right. You ready? I'm scared.
Yosh! Jaa, Music Starto!
Alright! Then, Music Start!
鉄の弾が正義の証明
An iron bullet is the proof of justice.
貫けば英雄に近づいた
If it pierces through, I've come closer to being a hero.
その目を閉じて触れてみれば
If you close your eyes and touch it,
同じ形 同じ体温の悪魔
A devil with the same shape and body temperature.
僕はダメで あいつはいいの？
Why am I no good, but he is okay?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
Even though there was just a wall there.
生まれてしまった 運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of having been born.
僕らはみんな自由なんだから
Because we are all free.
鳥のように羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird,
どこへだって行けるけど
I could go anywhere, but
帰る場所がなければ
if I don't have a place to return to,
きっとどこへも行けない
I surely can't go anywhere.
ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
I just hate to simply exist.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel.
それでも君を愛すよ
Even so, I will love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I sacrifice,
それでも君を守るよ
even so, I will protect you.
間違いだとしても
Even if it's a mistake,
疑ったりしない
I won't doubt it.
正しさとは自分のこと
Righteousness is to strongly believe
強く信じることだ
in yourself.
Darou?
Right?
How was... how do you feel?
Was it refreshing?
Refreshing right?
That was great.
素晴らしい体験をさせて頂きました。
I had a wonderful experience.
痛った...
It hurt...
All right, I feel like the scores are in.
Shall we see?
Ja-jan!
Ta-da!
Whoa!
That concludes the second half!
My big toe still hurts so bad.
みんな痛がってます、タクタさん。
Everyone is in pain, Takuta-san.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
痛気持ちよかったです。
It hurt but felt good.
I present to you, the final scores!
The one and only first place with 151.858 points is...
Ouro Kronii!
Yes! The healthiest of us all!
How do you feel?
Oh, I wish I got a massage for my left side too...
...that would have been so nice. But you know...
I'm so happy that we got to suffer together.
Yeah! Yay!
Okay. Now with that wholesome moment aside...
Yeah, let's get back to the la-
Not yet.
No, not yet.
We should get back to the live!
It's time for the punishment game.
Staff-san, please prepare. Thank you.
Okay, so they said it was a super sour drink?
Yes, I heard it's a sour drink.
It smells... It smells healthy.
It smells ass.
Is it Ume? It smells Ume.
Yeah... Ugh, isn't it stinky?
Okay, let's do it. Three unhealthy people.
Sabotose!
Kampai!
Cheers!
That sounds wonderful.
Ume!
It's Ume!
That's actually really good.
Really? Are you good?
It tastes better after a bit more time...
My face is turning into that lemon meme.
Okay, so we're gonna return to the live performance.
And the second half includes new songs,
so let's keep it going guys!
Let's go maggots!
Ah, you guys are fine. Okay let's get a move on.
ヘドが出るくらいにウザったいわ
You're so annoying I could puke.
ザッタイワ何つーかて面って
What's with that look on your face?
期待したあたしが馬鹿だった
I was an idiot to expect anything.
加害の圧倒美人
An overwhelmingly beautiful assailant.
それいいんじゃない？
Isn't that fine?
正気？
Are you sane?
浅いキャパシティ
Shallow capacity.
毎度おおきに
Thanks as always.
詰まるとこ人生ずっと地味
In the end, life is always plain.
右足左足
Right foot, left foot.
死ぬしかないのがいっそ
Might as well just die.
腹立たしいヤダだし
It's irritating, I hate it.
そろそろアクタ近づく惨事
Soon the trash approaches the tragedy.
ライフは反対はあたし
Life is the opposite of me.
似合い効率なんて馬鹿馬鹿しい
Matching efficiency is ridiculous.
聞き話せない関係
A relationship we can't speak of.
疎かしてしまいたいわ
I want to neglect it.
ダイダイ
Big Big
あなたのことあたし
I... you...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Hate you so, so, so, so, so much.
オーマイガー
Oh my god.
情けないもはや
It's pathetic, already...
バイバイバイバイバイしたい
I want to say bye bye bye bye bye.
脳内妄想の故に
Because of the delusion in my brain.
解解解解解はない
There is no solution.
頂戴私のことあなた
Give it to me, you...
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Hate me so, so, so, so, so much.
皆まで言うな
Don't say it all.
愛とかやって
Doing things like love...
一利なし
Not a single benefit.
Nothing マシマシ
Nothing increasing.
死んだらればねばでもニコニコ新橋
Even if dead, sticky, smiling at Shinbashi.
愛味して近づいて
Love the taste and come closer.
結末はボンミスボンミス
The ending is a careless mistake.
Thank you 拝命狂信
Thank you, fanatical obedience.
後味正気失せて暗いわ
The aftertaste makes me lose my sanity, it's dark.
いない
Absent.
大体
Basically,
あなたのこと
everything about you...
大嫌い
I hate, hate, hate, hate, hate you.
お前
You
が情けない
are pathetic.
もはやバイバイバイバイバイしたい
I already want to say bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
脳内
In my brain,
もう予測の
it's already predicted,
故に解解解解解はない
so there's no sol-sol-sol-solution.
土台
Fundamentally,
私のこと
about me...
あなた大嫌い
you hate, hate, hate, hate, hate me.
うらうらら
Ura urara
愛とか恋とかやって
Doing things like love and romance.
一二の死の Nothing
One, two, death's... Nothing.
もしもし
Hello, hello.
ならばならばだって鬼ごっこ血をWash
If so, if so, then let's play tag and wash the blood.
愛について気がついて
Realize what love is about.
始末はボミツボミツ
The conclusion is vomits, vomits.
Thank youは迷惑よ
'Thank you' is annoying.
後味一生嫌いたくないわ
I don't want to hate the aftertaste for the rest of my life.
Oh
Ahan
Yeah
I'm not into no one-way street
I'm gonna express my feelings in this song
H-A-L-F
簡単な英語しかわかんない
I only understand simple English.
踊るの大好き
I love dancing,
健康第一
health comes first.
憧れとコンプレックス大渋滞
Admiration and complexes in a heavy traffic jam.
カオスでノリノリ
Rocking out in the chaos.
カオスは飽き飽き
Sick and tired of the chaos.
差別されてる　いつもいつでも
Discriminated against, always and forever.
恵まれてるかどうかを
Whether I'm blessed or not...
楽しんでいたい
I want to enjoy it,
泣きたくないから
because I don't want to cry.
問い質す神様がいなくても
Even if there's no god to question.
もうかこつけていくしかないじゃん
I just have to use it as an excuse and keep going.
そのままこのまま
Just like that, just like this.
降り注ぐ光ね
The light pouring down, isn't it?
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as 'half'.
このままそのまま
Just like this, just like that.
突き進む光
The light that pushes forward.
意地悪なんかじゃ止まんない
I won't stop for something like nastiness.
笑わせたいのに
Even though I want to make you laugh,
上手にできない
I can't do it well.
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame it on anyone else.
生まれてみたいから
Because I want to try being born...
生まれてきただけ
I just came to be born.
新しいブーツと幸せ
New boots and happiness...
そんなに遠くはないでしょ
aren't that far away, right?
それでも今も誰かが
Even so, someone is still...
撃ち放つ悲しみと怒りの
shooting out sorrow and anger...
H-A-L-F
損をしたり
Taking losses...
ちょっと辛い
it's a little painful.
そんな日も
Even on days like that...
あるけど
they happen, but...
茨の道で
On this thorny path...
花が咲くなら
if flowers bloom,
絶対に
I absolutely...
逃せない
won't let them go.
もうかこつけていくしかないじゃん
I just have to use it as an excuse and keep going.
そのままこのまま
Just like that, just like this.
降り注ぐ光ね
The light pouring down, isn't it?
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as 'half'.
このままそのまま
Just like this, just like that.
突き進む光
The light that pushes forward.
X.U.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you
I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
we were all swept away
Don't take all of the weight
you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome
your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights
such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize
who I need
I'll be there, hold on
they'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
before you can be turned
illusions are torn
The fallen angels you run with
don't know
It is our pain
that makes us all human after all
Warm old safety, a photo to show
Our fragile precious world
Must protect it
respond to the call
Are they really deep
inside your head?
Do they control you
like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead
come in with me
Let me free the wings of your soul
can make it fly
We've been waiting here
just to make you whole again
No more hating see
I have always been your friend
No signs, no lights
such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize
who I need
I'll be there, hold on
they'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
the shadows appear
illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with
don't know
It is our pain
that makes us all human after all
Torn old safety, a photo to show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it
respond to the call
If you wanna fight with me
Then go ahead and fight with me
Cos all I wanna do is help you man
You will be the death of me
The power of our army
has been cut with a scythe
And if we lose you to them
we may never survive
You can leave
but you must first believe
Just one step at a time
and keep your head up boy and
You'll be free
Yay!
How was that so far?
That was good. How did... how do you feel?
That was good.
Do you guys like how it's been going so far on the songs?
Yeah!
We just had all of our duo songs.
Yeah.
And we also went through the variety part and...
...and everything, yeah.
How are you guys feeling? It still hurts.
I don't know how I... I don't know how I danced with... with this foot.
How are you guys? You're probably fine.
Oh, no, just... no, no.
You're fine. I'm not worried about you at all. How about you?
My foot still hurts. But it's okay!
Yeah!
There's a surprise at the end, but, before that...
We have an announcement about merchandise! Check this out!
Yeah! It's the Hololive English -Promise- 2nd Anniversary Celebration Merch!
We're releasing merchandise to commemorate our second anniversary.
Let's take turns introducing the merch, shall we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
So first up is a Frame Art Board of our wonderful Key Visual...
...for the Promise 2nd Anniversary.
The frame part uses a luxurious sparkling paper and the printed illustration...
...turns this into a high quality piece of art.
You definitely don't want to miss the chance to add it to your collection or room.
And guess what? You can even hang it on the wall!
Oh my god! On the wall!
Next up are the Collection Cards for each of Promise!
These cards feature an attractive design that are foil stamped on the front...
...and you can choose each card individually, so be sure to collect all of them!
Gotta collect 'em all! Wow!
Next we also have Ring Necklaces!
This design includes cute references and motifs for each of us.
You can use it as either a ring or a necklace...
...so feel free to change it up depending on the occasion.
And next we have special porcelain tumblers with our designs on them.
It features our talent colors on top of a black base.
They are designed to have a unified look...
...and I bet it will look so cool if you use several of these tumblers together...
...in like a drinking party or something.
And lastly, we have a 2-Way Tote Bag.
It's a 2-way design that can be used as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag.
It's even designed to be used as a carry-on bag too.
Perfect for traveling and convenience.
And to top it off, it has many pockets that will definitely be useful...
...for storing small items, like other merch!
Pockets! Oh my god!
And that concludes the Promise 2nd Anniversary Merch introduction!
Yay! Let's get it! Onegai shimasu!
Yay! Let's get it! Please!
And with that, we're finally at the very last part.
Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there would be a special, you know, surprise or announcement earlier.
Would you like to hear what it is?
Yes! Yes!
But... before that...
It's time for a stage change!
Whoa! Wait, what is going on?
Oh my god, we're floating! We're going up!
No! I refuse! Oh my!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait!
Okay, okay, we're good...
I'm getting... I'm getting claustrophobic!
I'm gonna be sick!
Oh, it's open!
I see the light!
Oh my goodness.
Okay.
Oh.
Ah, nice.
Ah, that's nice.
I feel fresh air.
Alrighty. Well, ladies, it is time for our final announcement.
Final announcement?!
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Finally releasing! It's called Run Back 'Round!
Run Back 'Round!
Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song...
and it's really cool, really catchy. It's quite different to...
you know, a lot of the original songs that Promise has put out before, so...
Different genre.
Yeah, we hope that you guys will listen to it a lot.
The chorus part is quite hype and honestly quite easy to remember...
so I feel like, you know, hopefully it becomes an earworm...
and you can put it on loop over and over and over again.
Over and over again.
That's our big reveal! Hope you're excited!
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited.
Well, I think... I think all that's left is for us to perform our new song.
What? We're gonna perform it here?
Right here. Floating here.
Floating here.
In the city!
But, before we go, do you have any final thoughts about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this as Promise...
and you know it was a lot of fun singing all those songs with you guys, different duets.
And I just really like the fact that we have a hideout now.
We do! We finally have a hideout now!
We have a bar too!
A bar! Celebration!
Catch you at the bar.
Big window.
I guess... it's in a fabulous location.
Imagine how expensive the rent is.
We don't need to pay for it. We don't pay for it. Oh good.
So... yeah, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
Yeah, I'm just really thankful that...
...you know, we're still here after two years.
And you know, hope everyone continues to support Promise. Thank you guys!
And here's to many, many more! Yay!
I could say the same thing.
I'm just gonna steal everyone and say that it's been great being with all of you for two years...
And, you know, now we get to have this cool hideout...
...and this awesome song that we get to show everyone. So, yay!
We ready?
Yes! I'm ready.
Let's go! Ready... se-no!
Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight...
Down in the streetlights...
Looking for a spotlight...
Making my move.
I'm running.
We go, woah!
Days like a whirlwind...
Don't stop comin'...
Got me in a tailspin...
What can I do?
Keep running!
We go, woah!
Lost and found...
...back to where I started.
I won't stay down...
...trust me I can do it.
I live life loud...
...take it to the limit.
So stand up proud...
...now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round...
...it's a new beginning.
I run back 'round...
...got to keep believing.
...I know where I'm going.
I run back 'round...
...nothing's gonna stop me now.
Whoa, oh, oh! Oh! Whoa, oh, oh!
Oh! Whoa, oh, oh! Oh! I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement...
Dreams in the distance...
Gotta be relentless...
Faster than sound...
Keep running!
We go, woah!
Oh yeah... Lock it and load it
僕らはexplosive
We are explosive
Swifter and lighter
明日もきっとbrighter
Tomorrow will surely be brighter
Faster than lightning
About to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round!
It's a new beginning
I run back 'round!
Got to keep believing
I know where I'm going
Day and night I'm running
I run back 'round!
Nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah, oh, oh!
止まらないよ！
Won't stop!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
走って 走って 走って
Run, run, run
I'm gonna run back 'round!
始まるよ
It's starting
I'm coming around
叶えるよ
I'll make it come true
I've got a dream just waiting now
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Yeah, everybody
Yeah, everybody come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!